Hello, Jia Lin.
مرحبا جيا لين.
How is it, Director Zhang?
كيف الحال ، المخرج تشانغ؟
Have you decided on the project with Ms. Xu?
هل قررت المشروع مع السيدة شو؟
Three novels and five plays.
ثلاث روايات وخمس مسرحيات.
I can't finish it in two weeks.
لا أستطيع أن أنهيها في غضون أسبوعين.
Who told you to read the whole book?
من قال لك أن تقرأ الكتاب كله؟
Didn't Miss Xu say
لم يغيب شو يقول
Just read the synopsis?
فقط اقرأ الملخص؟
How can we just look at the outline?
كيف يمكننا فقط إلقاء نظرة على الخطوط العريضة؟
These are all
هذه كلها
I sincerely sent you.
لقد أرسلت لك بصدق.
If I don't finish it,
إذا لم أنتهي منه ،
How to communicate with others?
كيف تتواصل مع الاخرين؟
You're the director.
أنت المخرج.
Don't you have a screenwriter?
أليس لديك كاتب سيناريو؟
Ms. Xu found it for you.
وجدتها السيدة شو من أجلك.
Are all first-rank screenwriters.
جميعهم من كتاب السيناريو من المرتبة الأولى.
The screenwriter is amazing.
كاتب السيناريو مذهل.
I have to keep up with the rhythm.
لا بد لي من مواكبة الإيقاع.
If I don't figure out the plot,
إذا لم أكتشف الحبكة ،
I'm not at ease.
لست مرتاحا.
Don't be too anxious.
لا تكن قلقا جدا.
Go out for a walk.
اخرج للنزهة
Leave the studio.
اترك الاستوديو.
Don't look at anything today.
لا تنظر إلى أي شيء اليوم.
Okay, I got it.
حسنا حصلت عليه.
Get back to work.
عد الى العمل.
bye-bye
مع السلامة
one's master's/teacher's son who is older than oneself
ابن المعلم / المعلم الأكبر منه
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Jingmei
جينغمي
I'm waiting for Jialin.
أنا أنتظر جيالين.
Jialin is not here today.
جيالين ليست هنا اليوم.
I'll go back.
سأعود.
one's master's/teacher's son who is older than oneself
ابن المعلم / المعلم الأكبر منه
Sorry, Jingmei.
آسف جينغمي.
To avoid it,
لتجنب ذلك ،
I can't take you home.
لا استطيع اصطحابك للمنزل.
Jia Lin will be unhappy.
لن تكون جيا لين سعيدة.
I didn't mean that.
لم أقصثد ذلك
I want to say that
أريد أن أقول أن
If you and Jia Lin go on like this,
إذا استمررت أنت وجيا لين هكذا ،
It's not a problem.
ليست مشكلة.
Is there anything I can do to help?
هل هناك أي شيء يمكنني القيام به للمساعدة؟
No,
رقم،
Before I asked Jia Lin to watch a movie,
قبل أن أطلب من جيا لين مشاهدة فيلم ،
I have to stay away from girls.
يجب أن أبتعد عن الفتيات.
Especially like you.
خاصة مثلك.
Such a beautiful girl.
يالها من فتاة جميلة.
Understand
يفهم
You're going to watch a movie?
أنت ذاهب لمشاهدة فيلم؟
When
متي
I can ask her out for you.
يمكنني أن أطلب منها الخروج من أجلك.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Really
حقًا
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
She and I are looking at
هي وأنا ننظر
The film I took before
الفيلم الذي التقطته من قبل
It's an alpaca.
إنها الألبكة.
In previous lives,
في الحياة السابقة ،
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Let's see which one.
دعونا نرى أي واحد.
This, this...
هذا هذا...
Please.
لو سمحت.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Good, Senior Brother.
جيد ، الأخ الأكبر.
Bye
وداعا
very small
صغير جدا
Commander Dong is here.
القائد دونغ هنا.
I'm here today.
انا هنا اليوم.
I have two words to tell you.
لدي كلمتين لأخبرك بهما.
The first sentence.
الجملة الأولى.
I'm going to play tonight.
انا ذاهب للعب الليلة.
Tonight's flight
رحلة الليلة
Go to the airport later.
اذهب إلى المطار لاحقًا.
For how long?
إلى متى؟
The second sentence.
الجملة الثانية.
I'll definitely win this competition.
سأفوز بالتأكيد في هذه المسابقة.
When I win the championship,
عندما فزت بالبطولة ،
I will come back and marry you.
سأعود وأتزوجك.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
He's so handsome.
انه وسيم جدا.
You're so happy.
انت سعيد جدا.
Hurry, open it.
على عجل ، افتحه.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
very small
صغير جدا
Pack three servings of chicken soup for me.
جهز لي ثلاث حصص من شوربة الدجاج.
What's up
ما أخبارك
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Really?
هل حقا؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Let me tell you something.
دعني أقول لك شيئا.
Jing Mei, you didn't know.
جينغ مي ، أنت لا تعرف.
Jing Mei wants three chicken soup.
جينغ مي يريد ثلاث حساء دجاج.
Pack your things.
وضب أغراضك.
good
جيد
Okay, Luo Xiao Xiao.
حسنًا ، لوه شياو شياو.
To do something shameful.
لفعل شيء مخجل.
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
No.
رقم.
Have you finished the script?
هل انتهيت من النص؟
Why did you buy so many chicken soup?
لماذا اشتريت الكثير من حساء الدجاج؟
They stay up all night fighting for blood.
يبقون مستيقظين طوال الليل يقاتلون من أجل الدم.
Are you playing chicken soup?
هل تلعب حساء الدجاج؟
Can you handle it?
هل يمكنك تولي الامر؟
It's for Long Yi.
إنه لـ Long Yi.
The beauty salon is very busy recently.
صالون التجميل مشغول للغاية في الآونة الأخيرة.
I didn't have time to eat.
لم يكن لدي وقت لتناول الطعام.
To make up for him.
للتعويض عنه.
Yes?
نعم؟
To be a good wife and a good mother.
أن تكون زوجة صالحة وأم صالحة.
Why are you jealous?
لماذا تغار؟
Are you in a relationship?
هل أنت مرتبط؟
young man
شاب
The mask is pretty good.
القناع جيد جدا
How old are you?
كم عمرك؟
Auntie, I'm 25 years old.
عمتي ، عمري 25 سنة.
If you like it,
إذا أعجبك ذلك ،
You can come often.
يمكنك أن تأتي في كثير من الأحيان.
This young man is so patient.
هذا الشاب صبور جدا.
He's a good man.
إنه رجل طيب.
Have you found someone?
هل وجدت شخص ما؟
I have it.
انا أملكه.
So young.
شاب جدا.
And became a boss.
وأصبح رئيسا.
It has a bright future.
لها مستقبل مشرق.
What do you belong to?
الى ماذا تنتمي؟
Auntie, I'm a dragon.
عمتي ، أنا تنين.
My eldest brother's niece
ابنة أخي الأكبر
And graduated from college.
وتخرجت من الكلية.
Working in a bank.
العمل في البنك.
Really, aunt?
حقا يا عمة؟
I have a niece in a foreign company.
لدي ابنة أخت في شركة أجنبية.
I earn a lot a month.
أكسب الكثير في الشهر.
She has a house and a car.
لديها منزل وسيارة.
Really, aunt?
حقا يا عمة؟
Actually, aunt,
في الواقع يا عمة
I'm married.
انا متزوج.
what
ماذا او ما
How old are you?
كم عمرك؟
Girlfriend doesn't count.
صديقة لا تحسب.
You're a good man.
أنت رجل طيب.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Honey, business is booming.
عزيزتي ، العمل مزدهر.
Honey, you're here.
عزيزتي ، أنت هنا.
Take a rest.
خذ راحة.
It's my turn.
انه دوري.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Sister, I'm serving you now.
أخت ، أنا أخدمك الآن.
It might be a little cold.
قد يكون الجو باردا قليلا.
How is the feeling
كيف هو الشعور
It's good.
إنه جيد.
It's comfortable.
انها مريحة.
The mask is comfortable.
القناع مريح.
You should come often.
يجب أن تأتي في كثير من الأحيان.
I'll definitely come here more often.
بالتأكيد سآتي إلى هنا في كثير من الأحيان.
Sure, honey.
بالتأكيد عزيزي.
Yes, I have.
نعم لدي.
Brother Qiang, what time are you coming?
الأخ تشيانغ ، في أي وقت ستأتي؟
Why are you still not here?
لماذا ما زلت غير موجود؟
I've arrived.
لقد وصل.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Sir
سيد
Would you like to serve now?
هل ترغب في الخدمة الآن؟
Hold on.
يتمسك.
OK
نعم
feed
تغذية
Xuan Yi.
شوان يي.
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
sorry
آسف
I'm busy now.
أنا مشغول الآن.
I'm not eating with you today.
أنا لا آكل معك اليوم.
It's my treat.
على حسابي.
That's me.
هذا أنا.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I won't let him come.
لن أتركه يأتي.
He wouldn't.
لم يفعل.
He insisted on missing you.
أصر على افتقادك.
His body
جسده
How could I take such a long flight?
كيف يمكنني أن أقوم برحلة طويلة كهذه؟
This is...
هذا هو...
If I wasn't careful,
إذا لم أكن حذرا ،
In the bathroom on the plane.
في الحمام على متن الطائرة.
And fell.
و سقط.
Yes
نعم
dad
بابا
grandpa
الجد
Xuan Yi is here.
شوان يي هنا.
To see you.
لرؤيتك.
I've recovered everything.
لقد استعدت كل شيء.
grandpa
الجد
You're disobedient again.
أنت غير مطيع مرة أخرى.
He's fine.
انه على ما يرام.
But the foot injury
لكن اصابة القدم
I need to stay in the hospital for observation.
أحتاج إلى البقاء في المستشفى للمراقبة.
You need to be hospitalized?
أنت بحاجة لدخول المستشفى؟
Can't you take care of her at home?
ألا يمكنك الاعتناء بها في المنزل؟
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
Uncle
اخو الام
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
You've been tired for a whole day.
لقد كنت متعبًا طوال اليوم.
Go back and rest.
العودة والراحة.
I'll handle the hospitalization procedures for Grandpa.
سأتعامل مع إجراءات العلاج في المستشفى للجد.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Go and handle the formalities.
اذهب والتعامل مع الإجراءات الشكلية.
I'll leave when you come back.
سأغادر عندما تعود.
Boss
رئيس
Can this really attract money?
هل يمكن أن يجذب هذا المال حقًا؟
Hello, please have your meal.
مرحبا ، من فضلك تناول وجبتك.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
wife
زوجة
Wonton is here.
فطيرة باللحم هنا.
eat
تأكل
husband
الزوج
You worked so hard for so many days.
لقد عملت بجد لأيام عديدة.
That's it?
هذا هو؟
I can treat you better.
يمكنني أن أعاملك بشكل أفضل.
This is delicious.
هذا شهي.
Is it so delicious?
هل هو لذيذ جدا؟
Delicious. I come here every day.
لذيذ.  آتي إلى هنا كل يوم.
You know the boss well.
أنت تعرف الرئيس جيدًا.
Come on, honey.
هيا عزيزتي.
husband
الزوج
You've changed.
لقد تغيرت.
I swear to you.
اقسم لك.
I only love you.
أنا أحبك فقط.
I really...
أنا في الحقيقه...
I only love you, Zhang Jingmei.
أنا فقط أحبك يا تشانغ جينغمي.
Eat it.
كلها.
grandpa
الجد
Eat more apples when you're free.
تناول المزيد من التفاح عندما تكون متفرغًا.
Apple is good for health.
التفاح مفيد للصحة.
It will help you recover.
سوف يساعدك على التعافي.
good
جيد
Yes
نعم
Anyway, when you're free,
على أي حال ، عندما تكون متفرغًا ،
I will come to visit you.
سوف آتي لزيارتك.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm here to see Grandpa.
أنا هنا لأرى جدي.
Who's your grandfather?
من هو جدك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Xuan Yi.
شوان يي.
Luo is a guest.
لوه ضيف.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Where is Uncle?
اين العم؟
I asked him to go back first.
طلبت منه العودة أولاً.
He's working hard.
إنه يعمل بجد.
I mean, you...
انا اعنيك انت...
Why are you so impulsive?
لماذا أنت مندفع جدا؟
We are a family.
نحن عائلة.
Who is your family?
من هي عائلتك
I
أنا
Come on, Grandpa.
تعال يا جدي.
Move up. Slowly.
تحرك.  ببطء.
Alright, alright.
حسنا حسنا.
Can I, Grandpa?
هل يمكنني يا جدي؟
It's comfortable like this.
إنه مريح مثل هذا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Do you remember this leg?
هل تتذكر هذه الساق؟
You can't push hard.
لا يمكنك الدفع بقوة.
If you want to lie down again,
إذا كنت تريد الاستلقاء مرة أخرى ،
Call me again.
اتصل بي مرة أخرى.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What?
ماذا؟
Nothing. Give it back to me.
لا شئ.  أعدها الي.
Just throw it away.
فقط ارميها بعيدا.
other
آخر
Something's wrong.
هناك خطأ.
You're so fast.
أنت سريع جدا.
An acquaintance committed the crime.
ارتكب أحد معارفه الجريمة.
What acquaintance committed the crime?
أي معارف ارتكب الجريمة؟
I bought it myself.
اشتريتها بنفسي.
Are you lying?
هل تكذب؟
Would you spend money on such a stupid thing?
هل تنفق المال على مثل هذا الشيء الغبي؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
They won it back.
لقد استعادوها.
Which one?
أيها؟
hate
يكره
You're here today.
أنت هنا اليوم.
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
لماذا لم تخبرني مسبقا؟
You didn't tell me your grandfather was ill.
أنت لم تخبرني أن جدك كان مريضًا.
Why should I tell you?
لماذا اقول لك
I can do it alone.
أستطيع أن أفعلها بمفردي.
Chen Xuanyi
تشن شواني
You should know that
عليك ان تعلم ذلك
You have a boyfriend.
لديك صديق.
No matter what happens in the future,
بغض النظر عما سيحدث في المستقبل ،
You must inform me immediately.
يجب أن تخبرني على الفور.
Can't bear it alone.
لا أستطيع تحمله بمفرده.
Don't answer the phone.
لا ترد على الهاتف.
Or disappear.
أو تختفي.
Do you know?
هل تعرف؟
Did you hear that?
هل سمعت هذا؟
OK!
نعم!
You pissed me off.
لقد أغضبتني.
This is BB cream.
هذا كريم BB.
I see.
أرى.
Why is it CC frost again?
لماذا هو CC frost مرة أخرى؟
wife
زوجة
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Beauty Center
مركز تجميل
Good boy.
ولد جيد.
He's not ashamed.
إنه لا يخجل.
sit
يجلس
I've asked someone to check it.
لقد طلبت من شخص ما التحقق من ذلك.
To be exact,
لأكون أكثر دقة،
Is a small store.
هو متجر صغير.
Can't reach the size of a beauty salon.
لا يمكن أن تصل إلى حجم صالون التجميل.
The jewelry store is closed.
متجر المجوهرات مغلق.
He opened a beauty salon.
افتتح صالون تجميل.
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك.
At least I'm not losing my temper.
على الأقل أنا لا أفقد أعصابي.
Oh that's true!
أوه هذا صحيح!
This young master
هذا السيد الشاب
This day, my God, I'm busy.
هذا اليوم يا إلهي أنا مشغول.
Old Li.
قديم لي.
You mean he opened a jewelry store?
تقصد أنه فتح محل مجوهرات؟
It's okay to get us a car full of jewelry.
لا بأس في أن تحضر لنا سيارة مليئة بالمجوهرات.
This beauty salon
صالون التجميل هذا
If I bring back a car full of masks,
إذا أحضرت سيارة مليئة بالأقنعة ،
Where should I put it?
أين أضعه؟
You can paste it.
يمكنك لصقه.
I
أنا
Are all high quality goods.
كلها سلع ذات جودة عالية.
My old face
وجهي القديم
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
Master Kitano.
سيد كيتانو.
Look at this bottle.
انظر إلى هذه الزجاجة.
It's so obvious that Master Kitano
من الواضح جدًا أن السيد كيتانو
Full of creativity.
مليئة بالإبداع.
Is this the smell of art?
هل هذه رائحة الفن؟
It's from buying coffee beans in Brazil.
إنه من شراء حبوب البن في البرازيل.
this
هذه
This dog can do that.
هذا الكلب يمكنه فعل ذلك.
It's lifelike.
إنه نابض بالحياة.
It's a leopard.
إنه نمر.
This is really a leopard.
هذا حقا نمر.
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
Young Master Long,
السيد الشاب لونج ،
You've been waiting for me all morning.
كنت تنتظرني طوال الصباح.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Master Kitano.
سيد كيتانو.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
I opened a beauty shop.
فتحت محل تجميل.
I want you to promote it for me.
أريدك أن تروج له من أجلي.
You know a lot of beautiful women.
أنت تعرف الكثير من النساء الجميلات.
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
My relationships are simple.
علاقاتي بسيطة.
I won't tell Chen Xuanyi.
لن أخبر تشين Xuanyi.
What are you panicking about?
ما الذي يزعجك؟
The real Master Kitano.
السيد الحقيقي كيتانو.
I have so many customers.
لدي الكثير من العملاء.
I'm counting on you.
انا اعتمد عليك.
No
رقم
Are you really using me as a mascot?
هل حقا تستخدمني كتعويذة؟
No,
رقم،
Brother
أخ
Brother, the finished product is ready.
أخي ، المنتج النهائي جاهز.
good
جيد
Long Yi.
لونغ يي.
That's what I want to deliver.
هذا ما أريد تقديمه.
That's not a money cat.
هذا ليس قطة المال.
Hello, Miss Su.
مرحبا انسة سو.
How do you know my surname is Su?
كيف تعرف أن لقبي هو سو؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Package yard
ساحة التعبئة
Yes
نعم
To support Yinzhen,
لدعم Yinzhen ،
It's really bleeding.
إنه ينزف حقًا.
Yu Qiu.
يو تشيو.
Jialin
جيالين
Are you really here?
هل انت حقا هنا
You've grown up, Yu Hao Qiu.
لقد كبرت يا يو هاو كيو.
You learned to cheat me by working with Zhang Jingmei.
لقد تعلمت خداعي من خلال العمل مع Zhang Jingmei.
I'll find her.
سوف أجدها.
Don't.
لا.
Jialin, Jialing.
جيالين ، جيالينغ.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
You always said that
كنت دائما تقول ذلك
Did I never do anything for you?
ألم أفعل شيئًا من أجلك أبدًا؟
I booked the show.
لقد حجزت العرض.
Only for you.
فقط من اجلك.
Yu Qiu.
يو تشيو.
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
I want to get you back.
أريد أن أعيدك.
Jialin
جيالين
I really know I was wrong.
أنا أعلم حقًا أنني كنت مخطئًا.
I won't be a man anymore.
لن أكون رجلاً بعد الآن.
No, no.
مهووس.
I just want to be a warm man for you.
أنا فقط أريد أن أكون رجلاً دافئًا من أجلك.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
What should I do in the future?
ماذا علي أن أفعل في المستقبل؟
Only for you.
فقط من اجلك.
I only have eyes for you.
انا فقط امتلك عيون لاجلك.
I only have you in my heart.
أنا فقط أملك في قلبي.
Please forgive me, Jia Lin.
أرجوك سامحني يا جيا لين.
Yu Qiu.
يو تشيو.
Don't tell me.
لا تخبرني.
You sent me so many movie tickets.
لقد أرسلت لي الكثير من تذاكر السينما.
You booked the show.
لقد حجزت العرض.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Look at this cinema.
انظر إلى هذه السينما.
Although it's far away,
على الرغم من أنه بعيد ،
But my apology
لكن اعتذاري
But there's no discount at all.
لكن لا يوجد خصم على الإطلاق.
Yu Hao Qiu, are you crazy?
يو هاو تشيو ، هل أنت مجنون؟
Have you paid off the car loan?
هل سددت قرض السيارة؟
Is the mortgage paid off?
هل الرهن مسدد؟
You have too much money to spend, right?
لديك الكثير من المال لتنفقه ، أليس كذلك؟
How much is this bag?
كم سعر هذه الحقيبة؟
I didn't expect that
لم أتوقع ذلك
I can handle so many shows.
يمكنني التعامل مع العديد من العروض.
I thought you would come.
اعتقدت أنك ستأتي.
If it weren't for the lack of money,
لولا نقص المال ،
I can't choose here.
لا يمكنني الاختيار هنا.
I know you don't like
أعلم أنك لا تحب
A bad theater.
مسرح سيء.
Look at this theater.
انظر إلى هذا المسرح.
It's cheap.
إنه رخيص.
Now I know I care about money.
الآن أعرف أنني أهتم بالمال.
Jialin,
جيالين ،
What bad film?
ما الفيلم السيئ؟
Jialin, you laughed.
لقد ضحكت يا جيالين.